jobnewsusa.com 2017-02-11

# Privacy Policy – Job News

**Overview**

Job News is a network of career web sites that provide a forum for job seekers and employers to get in contact with each other. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our users and want to provide a safe, secure environment so that you will have a reasonable expectation of privacy. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the personal information you submit to us remains private and that any other information you give us will only be used for the intended purposes. You should also read and understand our Terms and Conditions (click here), which are incorporated into this Privacy Policy. We will work hard to earn your loyalty; therefore, the following reflects our commitment to you.

 **Information About You**

When you sign up for a job seeker account with Job News, you create a “account profile” (including information such as, but not limited to employment history, job title, salary requirements, education level, and job skills) by posting your resume information online. We also collect personal information (including your contact information or other information in which your identity is discernible), which becomes part of your private account profile. An employer may view your contact information only when you apply to a specific job(s), and with the implicit intention of contacting you regarding potential employment opportunities.

When you sign up for an employer account with Job News, you may create  “job postings,” the content of which is made available online via our (and sometimes our affiliates’) web sites. We also collect personal information (including your contact information or other information in which your identity is discernible), which becomes part of your private “account profile.” Job seekers may view your public information with the implicit intention of contacting you regarding your (or your client’s) potential employment opportunities.

Regardless of your account type, from time to time, you may supply us supplemental information (such as, interests, favorites, preferences, gender, age group, hobbies, etc.) so we can better deliver personalized services. Unless you tell us otherwise, we may use this information to make you aware of opportunities, job openings, services, products, site changes, etc., which we believe may be of interest to you. Providing supplemental information is strictly voluntary, and you will not be subject to any adverse action or treatment if you choose not to provide such information. We respect your account’s communication settings.

 **Job Seeker Resume Information**

You may post one (1) resume at a time. What you put in any resume must be true and accurate to the best of your knowledge. Job News is under no obligation to verify any information you supply, including your identity. Your resume(s) won't be accessible to employers other than those offering specific job(s) to which you specifically apply.

You may edit or delete a resume at any time. However, customers and other users of our site may have already retained a copy of your resume in their own files. Job News is not responsible for the use, retention or disclosure of any resumes or other information about you that has been posted publicly at any time.

General Information Disclosure

Your public profile will be accessible to all our customers who pay for access (including employers, advertisers, recruiters, headhunters, human resource professionals, data aggregators, marketers, or government agencies, such as law enforcement and national security agencies). Depending on what you put in your resume and public profile, it is possible that your current employer or other person may learn that you are looking for a job. Job News is not responsible for the disclosure of any information that you have made public.

We do not disclose information about you to any third parties, unless:

\- you consent to such disclosure, or indicate you would like to receive information about the products or services of third parties

\- it is required by companies we employ to perform functions on our behalf, such as processing or analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, or providing customer service.

\- it is required by a court or requested by a law enforcement agency and we believe it is reasonably necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of Job News; (c) prevent a crime or aide national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.

\- a third party acquires a substantial portion of our company or assets, whether by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of stock or assets, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding.

 **Affiliates**

Job News, as used throughout this agreement, includes any affiliates that we may control, may be controlled by, or with whom we do business. Job News has partnering arrangements with various newspapers, broadcast media, recruiting companies, advertisers, and others in the career industry. If you have come to Job News by a link from an affiliate or advertiser site, you should read and be familiar with their terms and privacy policies because Job News has no control over and is not responsible for the practices of other web sites.

Job News shares services with affiliate sites to power recruitment areas on their web sites. Personal or demographic information you supply to affiliate sites may become part of Job News data, and vice versa. Information gathered on a page for an affiliate site may become the property of the other site or of both Job News and the other site. In that instance, the use of such information by the affiliate site may be subject to their privacy policy. Job News is not responsible for any affiliate site’s use of your personal or demographic information.

 **Updating Your Account**

Job News allows you to change or correct your personal or public information at any time, including removal or replacement of your resume and any profile information. To do so, simply log into your account, go to your account profile, and you will find options for editing the information you have submitted. However, users who may have previously accessed the web site may have retained a copy of your resume or an earlier version of it; therefore, we cannot be responsible for the retention, use or privacy of any resumes that have been posted on our site, or for their unauthorized use or disclosure by or to third parties under these circumstances.

 **Security**

Job News has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. When you place an order online with Job News, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. Job News uses a PCI-compliant third-party service company to process its credit card transactions.

 **Credit Card Information**

If you use a credit card to pay for any Job News services or products, we may retain your credit card information in order to renew your account in the event you elect to renew your subscription. When we do retain credit card information, we keep it secure and separate from other demographic information you may have given us. We do not share credit card information internally within divisions of Job News.

 **Children**

Job News is directed to adults and not to children under the age of 13. However, we cannot prohibit minors from visiting our web site, so we must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervising children under 13 to decide which materials are appropriate for such children to view and/or purchase. You must be at least 13 to use this web site, and minors under the age of 18 must have their parent's consent before providing any information to Job News. Parents are encouraged to monitor and supervise their children’s use of this and every web site. Job News complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and does not permit registration by and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13.

 **Information About All Visitors**

Job News collects general usage information about all visitors of our site, such as what areas of the site they visit most frequently and what services they access the most. This information may also include IP addresses, browser types, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. However, we only use such usage data anonymously. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you. We may share this information with our affiliates, but only anonymously and in the aggregate so that they too may understand how Job News visitors use our site and can help create a better overall experience.

Specifically, Job News uses Google Analytics to track website usage. In addition to general usage information, we also collect data for:

By enabling the Advertising Features, Job News uses Google Analytics to collect data about our website traffic via [Google advertising cookies](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/types/) and [anonymous identifiers](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/key-terms/#toc-terms-identifier), in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation. Job News doesn't facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information collected through any Google advertising product. In other words, your personal information is kept private, because Job News respects your privacy.

 **Cookies**

To enhance your experience at Job News, we may use features of your web browser called cookies, beacons, Flash cookies or similar. Cookies are small files that your browser places on your computer's hard drive for remembering your past visits, including user names, passwords and preferences, tracking click streams, and load balancing. Cookies help us provide you better, faster, personalized service. You have the option of setting your browser to reject or restrict the use of cookies, although doing so may hinder performance and negatively impact or limit your use of our site. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information, including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the beacon resides, to help count users who have visited certain pages.

 **Records Retention**

We retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use with us more efficient, practical and relevant, and for archival purposes. You can correct or update your profile and resume at any time, or delete them from the online database, in which event we will remove all our copies of your profile or resume from the web site, except for an archival copy of the data which is not accessible to customers. We cannot make any guarantee as to the records retention or destruction of third parties who may have lawfully obtained or made copies of your resume or other public information.

 **Feedback**

We may have an area on the web site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback submitted through this area becomes the property of Job News. By posting such information, you agree that Job News may use your feedback, including success stories, for marketing purposes or to contact you for further feedback on the site. Job News may also have public forums and chat rooms, so any information you publicly provide there shall be subject to our acceptable use policy and under no control of Job News.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please review our Terms and Conditions of Use (click here) which govern your use of this web site. If you have any questions whatsoever, you should contact your attorney. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, any changes will be posted here so that you will always know what our Privacy Policy is, what information we gather, how we use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If at any time you have questions or concerns about Job News' Privacy Policy or terms and conditions of use, please feel free to email us or call 1-888-502-6397 and ask to speak with one of our representatives.

 **Contact Information**

Job News and JobNewUSA are assumed names for United Metro Media, LLC, a Kentucky Limited Liability Company, with its principal offices at 9000 Wessex Place, Suite 202, Louisville, Jefferson County, Kentucky, telephone (888) 502-6397. All notices should be sent to this address.

Thank you for using Job News!
